(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T05:49:56.362167",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
堂々巡りのファンタジー
A proud, wandering fantasy,
アンソロジー 混ざる有象無象
an ungrounded melody mixing fact and fiction.
本能のままに行動不能に
Acting on pure instinct, unable to move,
高まる衝動 (ooh-ooh)
with surging impulses, ooh-ooh.
もう、どうなってもいいや
Oh, come what may!
当たり前のことが知りたいだけ
I just want to know what's natural,
星に願う本当の気持ち
my true feeling whispered to the stars.
苦し紛れの言い訳は いらない、意味ない
Painful, tangled excuses are unnecessary, meaningless.
君はどう思う？ (oh)
What do you think? (Oh)
行き場を失ったみたいだ
It's like losing where I belong,
心は棘の類で (ふー)
my heart is full of thorns. (Ooh)
おんなじことばかり繰り返して
Repeating the same old trivial things,
鳥籠の中で踊る (踊る)
dancing inside a birdcage. (Dancing)
ふ和っと浮かんで取り繕うまで
Floating up softly until I'm snatched away,
描いて泣き叫んで消えないように
drawing, crying out, so it won't vanish—
魔法みたいな都合いいもの
like magic, a convenient thing.
主人公なら起承転結
If I'm the protagonist, it's introduction, development, twist, and conclusion.
最後はどうなってもhappy ending
In the end, even if it's a happy ending,
それなら好きにさせてよ
then let me do as I please!
もう、どうなってもいいや
Oh, come what may!
真っ逆様に落ちていってた
Falling in completely the opposite direction,
無重力midnight逃避行
zero-gravity midnight evasion flight.
秘密の裏から交わして囁 (囁 oh, woah)
Crossing whispers from behind secrets (whispers, oh, woah),
一切合切持って言って
taking everything together,
余すことなく人生讃歌
a human life elegy without a thing to spare.
混ざり合う星に想い馳せて (ooh, yeah)
Sending thoughts to the blending stars (ooh, yeah),
月が綺麗だなんて
saying "The moon is beautiful,"
この世はすべてワンダー 愛を叫ぶ
as if this world is all a wonder, crying out for love.
曖昧な窓に揺れてる君の瞳の
Focusing right onto the depths
奥へとピント合わせてフォーカス (aw)
of your eyes swaying in the hazy window (ooh).
誰の触れたこともない 真実のその雨に濡れた体
Drenched in the truth's rain,
ざわつくひらめく簡単じゃないから
which nobody has ever touched—
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと盲目に
it's not so simple, it flutters and stirs.
どの道悩みは尽きないし
No matter which path, troubles never end,
いっそ望んでいる
so I might as well just wish for it.
嫌な予感がダダ溢れ
Bad omens overflow,
初めからそこントコ引き寄せて
pulling me in from the very start.
月の涙がぽたこのよは
As if the tears of the moon,
まるでストレンジャー
this world is practically a stranger,
愛を言いわせば
and I missed the chance to say goodbye.
気付けば隙間に落ちていった
Before I knew it, I fell right in,
真夜中涙引きこもを
midnight tears pulling me under.
秘密の中が交わってとりこ
Entwined in secret mysteries,
一切合切持って行って
carrying every single thing,
もうすることない人生を
to a completely different life.
混ざり合う星に思い馳せて
Letting my thoughts wander to the stars we crossed.
月が綺麗なんて
Even if the moon is lovely,
この夜は全て割んだ
this world broke it all down.
愛をしらば
I want to say goodbye.
ろくでもないのファンタジー
Fantasies spinning in my head,
うすら白い謎の作造
spinning in a chaotic dance of stars.
自分のままにほどくように
Tearing away at my own whim,
包み込む衝動
yielding to a sudden impulse.
もうどうだっていいや
Whatever, it doesn't even matter.
つまらないデイザもう散々ね!
Another boring day, nothing to show for it!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
Living a life just wishing for miracles.
Watch me do-do-do-do-do!
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Spellcraft secret trick, magic without a trick.
I wanna be free! だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free! But I'm still just faking.
(The party ain't started)
Heyタクシーちょっと宇宙過不足
Hey, taxi, just a bit of space travel.
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす
The second hand makes a sound, hurrying the night along.
魔界のように人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Like a monster, life is magic that melts in an instant,
それならば駆け抜けて想い通り!
so then run right through it just as you imagine!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってdrivin'
A fancy carriage, jump in and drivin',
あたちは大変身メイクアップ!
myself a total makeover!
我儘のままに爛れに注意
Pay attention to the dazzling gleam of my own will.
洒落た街でdancin'
Dancin' in a dazzling town,
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
goodbye to any sense of inferiority.
何時は飲采クラップオウデエンス
Whenever it is, let's harvest the crowd's applause.
皆々御詠和あれ!
Everyone, join in and sing along!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
混濁がっても仕樣が無い
Even if things get messy, it can't be helped.
ガラスシューズで踊るTonight
Dancing tonight in glass shoes.
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
今夜に明日など無い
There's no tonight or tomorrow,
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
so whoever dances freely wins, right?
Dance!ラリラリホ
Dance! Lalirari-ho,
どんな問題も解法は一つ
every problem has just one solution.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
Loving the blank page, the correct answer, and even mistakes.
本当のあたしの理想
The true ideal of who I am.
なんだか世界は限界の気がして
Somehow the world feels like it's reaching its limit,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
just seeking peace of mind.
今すぐjumpin', jumpin' out
Jump in, jumpin' out right now!
Chitty-chitty, bang-bang Chitty, bang-bang
いいダクダクに危機感抱く日々に
With a good 'da-da-da' and a sense of crisis growing daily,
ギリギリ爆発君
we're on the verge of exploding.
たった今発散してしまおうか
Let's just vent it all out right now!
まだまだビビダンタミタミに乱射
Still shooting beams at the binitaputami,
一発じゃあ打ち足りないわ
one shot isn't enough to strike.
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
An answer led me straight to you,
ハイになるまで踊っていよう
let's keep dancing until we're high!
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA)
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, yeah)
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってdrivin'
A fancy carriage, jump in and drivin',
あたちは大変身メイクアップ!
myself a total makeover!
我儘のままに爛れに注意
Pay attention to the dazzling gleam of my own will.
洒落た街でdancin'
Dancin' in a dazzling town,
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
goodbye to any sense of inferiority.
何時は飲采クラップオウデエンス
Whenever it is, let's harvest the crowd's applause.
皆々御詠和あれ!
Everyone, join in and sing along!
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA)
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, yeah)
混濁がっても仕樣が無い
Even if things get messy, it can't be helped.
ガラスシューズで踊るTonight
Dancing tonight in glass shoes.
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA)
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, yeah)
今夜に明日など無い
There's no tonight or tomorrow,
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
so whoever dances freely wins, right?
Dance!ラリラリホ
Dance! Lalirari-ho,
どんな問題も解法は一つ
every problem has just one solution.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
Loving the blank page, the correct answer, and even mistakes.
本当のあたしの理想
The true ideal of who I am.
なんだか世界は限界の気がして
Somehow the world feels like it's reaching its limit,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
just seeking peace of mind.
今すぐjumpin', jumpin' out
Jump in, jumpin' out right now!
Chitty-chitty, bang-bang Chitty, bang-bang
いいダクダクに危機感抱く日々に
With a good 'da-da-da' and a sense of crisis growing daily,
ギリギリ爆発君
we're on the verge of exploding.
たった今発散してしまおうか
Let's just vent it all out right now!
まだまだビビダンタミタミに乱射
Still shooting beams at the binitaputami,
一発じゃあ打ち足りないわ
one shot isn't enough to strike.
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
An answer led me straight to you,
ハイになるまで踊っていよう
let's keep dancing until we're high!
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA)
(BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, yeah)
見つめているばかり 手を伸ばして思い出す
Staring fixedly, reaching out and remembering
近づきたくないわね 聞かせたい声
I don't want to get close, the voice I want you to hear
可能性だ 君が誰なんだか知りたいんだ
It's a possibility, I want to know who you really are
証明しよう 僕ら本当はどうしたい？
Let's prove what we truly want to do
逃げたいと耳をさいだ しかも心臓を叩いてたスナイパー
A sniper covering their ears wanting to run, beating against the heart
変わらない表情に 答えを突き立てて
Thrusting the answer into that unchanging expression
情熱は月に向かって撃ってるスナイパー
Passion is a sniper shooting toward the moon
未来をどうやら君にしたい 喉が渇いてく 後悔はないわ
It seems I want my future to be with you, my throat gets dry, no regrets
擦り抜け埋めるの ナイテナインパーセント 小指には銃弾を
Slip through and fill it, 99%, a bullet on my pinky
本当はどうしたいんだっけ？ 愛してハートちょうだいって乗せて
What did I really want? Loaded with "love me, give me your heart"
ああ誰愛すの ああ一番乗りで踏み潰そう
Ah, who will you love? Ah, let's crush it first
ああ誰愛すの
Ah, who will you love?
ぶつかった壁も ぶつかり合った屑さも 息継ぎように照らす 絶品になれ
Even clashing walls, even colliding pieces of trash, illuminate like breaths, become exquisite
もしも人生が１０分なら ７分あなただけに捧げちゃくに
If life were 10 minutes, dedicating 7 minutes entirely to you
目を盗むようなアトラクションで タッチダウン
With an attraction that steals glances, touchdown
臆病を好きに燃やしていけマスター まだ見ぬトーンは君にしたい
Burn your cowardice as you like, master, I want the unseen tone to be yours
夢も照らす あったかくて機能じゃ 擦り抜け埋めるの ナイテナインパーセント
Illuminating dreams too, warm and functional... sliding through to fill 99%
甘ったるさを砕け 本当はどうしたいんだっけ？
Crush the sweetness, what did I really want?
追い付くわ ハートちょうだいって重ねて
Catching up, overlapping "give me your heart"
正面ショット 届くんだって
Frontal shot, reaching it
情熱は月に向かって撃ってるスナイパー 未来を今日も僕らにしたい
Passion is a sniper shooting toward the moon, wanting today's future to be ours
建てた笑ったって 臭い話は
Built, laughed, stinky talk is
擦り抜け埋めるの ナイテナインパーセント 小指には銃弾を
Sliding through to fill, 99%, a bullet on my pinky
本当はどうしたいんだっけ？ 愛してハートちょうだいって乗せて
What did I really want? Loaded with "love me, give me your heart"
ああ誰愛すの ああ一番乗りで
Ah, who will you love? Ah, being first
踏み潰そうの 擦り抜け埋めるの
Let's crush it, sliding through to fill
ナイテナインパーセント 飛び込んでいけ踏み潰そう
99%, dive in and crush it
あなただけに 飛び込んでいけ踏み潰そう
For you alone, dive in and crush it
綺麗事を吐くその口が 君のこと苦しめるから
That mouth that utters nice platitudes hurts you
苦しめるから
Hurts you
同じことばかりの日々には
In days that are all the same
君を求めて寄り添い合うの
We seek each other and snuggle close
節目の決まり合うから フィルターを送って
Because milestones clash, send a filter
散々占った 孤独の境界線は
The boundary line of solitude we divined over and over is
自分なりの生き方なの？ 偏屈な思考に縛られたまま
Is this my own way of living? Bound by stubborn thoughts
躓いたことだって もっと自分らしく
Even stumbling, more like myself
ぶつかり合った屑さも
Even the garbage pieces that clashed
綺麗事を吐くその口が 泣いだから歌を歌うんだ
That mouth uttering platitudes, since it cried, I sing a song
認めているその顔が 僕のこと曇らせる
That face acknowledging me makes me cloudy
こんな声だって ずっと笑えなくて
Even with a voice like this, I could never keep smiling
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて ずっと欲張って きっと間違いだって 今日も泥を零す 不完全
Wanting to spin more perfect words, always greedy, surely it's a mistake, spilling mud again today, imperfect
どんな朝も
Any morning...
どんな朝も言えない日常にはただ
In a daily life where I can't say a word,
理想なんてと笑え笑う声
I just laugh at ideals and such with a smile.
言い返す言葉も選べずに
Without even choosing words to retort,
ただ増していく痛み
the pain just builds up.
呼吸を貼る初動で屈して
Yielding to the initial impulse of breath,
綺麗なままで生きてたかった
I wanted to live on purely.
諦めを塗り重ねて 本当が見えなくなってしまったんだ
Piling up resignation until the truth became invisible.
戯言を吐くその口が
That mouth uttering nonsense—
戯言を吐くその口が嫌いだから歌うんだ
I hate that mouth, so I sing.
諦めているその顔が 君のこと苦しめる
That resigned face of yours torments you.
こんな声だって伝わらなくって もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
Even if this voice doesn't reach, I want to spin more perfect words.
ずっと欲張って 聞き間違えて それでも歌う
Always being greedy, mishearing, yet still singing.
不完全だから
Because it's imperfect.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
楽しんでますか？
Are you enjoying yourselves?
さあ、みんなね、武道館サイエンで出したあの重大発表のティザー、あの内容が気に気になっている頃なのではないでしょうか？
Now then, aren't you all curious about the content of that major announcement teaser we released at Budokan?
それからみんな、もちろん見つけてくれましたよね？
And of course, everyone found it, right?
先週の月曜日から、ある場所で屋外広告もね、出ていたりして
Since last Monday, outdoor ads have been put up in certain places,
きっと、今頃ね、何が起きるんだって、ただならぬ雰囲気を皆さん感じて、ドキマギしているんじゃないかなと思うんですけれども、
and I think you all must be feeling that unusual atmosphere wondering what's about to happen and feeling all nervous,
まずはね、えー、言葉じゃなくて、今日の告知に向けて、音楽に込めてみんなに伝えたいなと思い、こういう編成で今回やらせてもらっております。
first of all, rather than with words, I wanted to put my feelings into music for today's announcement, which is why we're doing this arrangement.
アコースティックってさ、なんか、えもくて、今までのことをこう思い出ような、なんかノスタルジーな気持ちになったりしますよね？
Acoustic music has this emotional vibe, making you reminisce about the past and feel a sort of nostalgia, doesn't it?
いつもは、テンションを上げてくれるようなあの曲が、今日はね、また違った形でみんなに響いたらいいなと思って、歌わせていただいております。
Songs that usually lift your spirits—I'm singing them today hoping they'll resonate with everyone in a different way.
楽曲のアレンジもそうだし、この生誕配信自体もそうだし、新しい一面を見せながらも、何よりこの8年間、みんなでね、一緒にやってきた、紡いできた、絆みたいなものがしっかり感じられるライブにできたら嬉しいです。
The song arrangements, this birthday stream itself... while showing a new side, above all, I'd be happy if this could be a live performance where we can strongly feel the bonds we've built together over these past 8 years.
それでは、次の曲に行きましょう。ムーンライト。
Well then, let's move on to the next song. Moonlight.
遠くまで歩こうよ 裸足で小さな幸せを見つけて 湿った月が窓の向こうに
Let's walk far away barefoot, finding small happiness, with the damp moon beyond the window...
こっちにおいでと笑った
laughing and saying, "Come over here."
一体もどうしてなんだよね案外分かり合えない部分も案牌
Why is it like this anyway? Even parts we can't quite understand are safe.
月明かりをめくった残像 誰かにとっての普通をしよう
Turning the moonlight's afterimage, let's act normal for someone's sake.
私と踊ってよ
Dance with me.
ムーンライトねえこっちで遊ぼうよ 一体何処探しても隠し言葉ばっかの人生
Moonlight, hey let's play over here. Looking anywhere, it's a life of hidden words.
ねぇこっちで遊ぼうよみんな
Hey, let's play over here, everyone.
面倒いカーテンを開けて寒々しい夜を抜け出そう
Opening troublesome curtains, let's slip out into the chilly night.
ただ言うことばっかで忙しいけど休む案の定意図せずに
We're just busy talking, but resting, sure enough, without intending to,
街をハイジャックしようぜ このメロんなきょうをずっと
let's hijack the town—let's keep this melody going all day today.
遠くまで歩こうよ、裸足で
Let's walk far away, barefoot
小さな幸せを見つけて
Searching for small happiness
湿った月が窓を覗いて
The damp moon peers into the window
こっちへおいらせと笑った
And laughed, telling me to come this way
似た者同士なんだよね、案外
We're surprisingly similar, aren't we
分かり合えない部分も安牌
Even the parts we don't understand are safe bets
私と踊ってよ、ムーンライト
Dance with me, moonlight
ねえ、こっちであそぼ サニーサイド
Hey, let's play on the sunny side
隠し事ばっかのインサイド
Inside, full of secrets
ねえ、こっちであそぼうよ ミッドナイト
Hey, let's play on the midnight
この、重たいカーテンを開けて
Open this heavy curtain
嘘みたいな夜を抜け出そう
Let's escape this dream-like night
まだ、やる事ばっかで忙しいけどおやすみ
There's still so much to do, but goodnight
あの、一等星になって
Becoming a first-magnitude star
街をハイジャックしようぜ
Let's hijack the city
この、メロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's swim through this mellow day forever
街明かりを奪って、月で待ち合わせ
Steal the city lights, meet at the moon
届きそうで届かない、あなたはムーンライト
You are the moonlight, reachable yet unreachable
理由もなく、寂しい夜が来て
For no reason, a lonely night comes
古くなっていく記憶の上で眠りたい
I want to sleep on top of aging memories
似た者同士なんだから、厄介
We're similar, so it's troublesome
隠し事すら抱えて、厄介
Even holding onto secrets is troublesome
まだ、やる事ばっかで忙しいけどおやすみ
There's still so much to do, but goodnight
あの、光の方へ、どこか遠い方へ
Toward the light, somewhere far away
この、メロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's swim through this mellow day forever
眠れそうで眠れない、こんな夜は
I want to sleep, but can't sleep on a night like this
隠し事ばっかのインサイド
Inside, full of secrets
ねえ、こっちであそぼうよ ミッドナイト
Hey, let's play on the midnight
街明かりを奪って、月で待ち合わせ
Steal the city lights, meet at the moon
届きそうで届かない、あなたはムーンライト
You are the moonlight, reachable yet unreachable
尽きない悩みの種、話を聞かせて
Tell me about the endless seeds of worry
私とあなただけの世界で
In a world just for you and me
こっちを向いてと笑った
And laughed, telling me to look this way
似た者同士なんだよね、案外
We're surprisingly similar, aren't we
分かり合えない部分も安牌
Even the parts we don't understand are safe bets
月明かりをめくった残像
An afterimage of the moonlight
私にとっての普通でいよう
Let's stay as normal for me
実は、ここからスペシャルゲストに来てもらっています。
Actually, we have a special guest joining us from here.
さあ、誰か分かるかな？
Now, do you know who it is?
それでは、お呼びいたしましょう！
Then, let's call them out!
伊野たくさん！
Ino-takusan!
お久しぶりです。
Long time no see.
改めまして、よろしくお願いします。
Once again, nice to work with you.
来てくれてうれしいです。ありがとうございます。
I'm so glad you could come. Thank you very much.
ここからは、伊野たくさんにも入ってもらって、さらなる特別編成で何曲か続けてお届けしていきますよ。伊野たくさん、準備はいいですか？
From here on, Ino-takusan will join us too, and we will deliver a few more songs with a special arrangement. Ino-takusan, are you ready?
よろしくお願いします。
Looking forward to it.
それでは、聞いてください。夜を待つよ。
Then, please listen. I'll Wait for the Night.
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
I'll wait for the night, I'll wait for the night
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I'll wait for the night, I'll wait
今日もまたばっちり しっかり決まってる
Everything's perfect and tight today
君ははっきりきっかり歌って
You're singing clearly and distinctly
明けない夜は そんなものはないよと
Saying "There's no such thing as a night that doesn't end"
椰子の木が ゆっくりゆっくりそよいでる
The palm trees are swaying slowly, slowly
僕はやっぱりさっぱりわからない ただひたすらに 夜を待つよ
I don't understand it at all, frankly. I'll just wait for the night, simply
このままじゃ だんだんダメになりそう 夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
Everything's gonna fall apart like this. I'll wait for the night, I'll wait for the night
きっとさんざんな目に遭いそう 夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I'm sure I'll have a terrible time. I'll wait for the night, I'll wait
耐え抜いて ざんざん雨に降られて 夜を待つよ 君を待つよ 待つのよ
Enduring it, pouring rain falls on me. I'll wait for the night, I'll wait for you, I'll wait
今は 待つのよ
I'm waiting now
濡れたまんま 切先を研ぐのよ
Soaking wet, sharpening the blade
いきあたりばったり にっこり笑って
Smiling smilingly at random
今日もごっこで ホットなふりして あかさたなさえ はまらないよ ロンリネス
Pretending to be hot with this make-believe again today. Can't even hit "a-ka-sa-ta-na," loneliness
もののけは あっちでこっちで踊って 君はハッタリ ばっかりかまして ぼくは 夜を待つよ
Mononoke are dancing over there, over here. You're bluffing all the time, and I'll wait for the night
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
Wait for the night, wait for the night...
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
Wait for the night, waiting for it.
今日もまたばっちり しっかりきまってる
Today again, it's set and locked tightly in place.
君ははっきり きっかり歌っている
You are singing clearly and decisively.
明けない夜はそんなものはないよと
They say there's no such thing as a night that doesn't end,
椰子の木がゆっくり ゆっくりそよいでる
And the palm trees sway slowly, slowly.
ぼくはやっぱり さっぱりわからない
I, as expected, don't understand it at all,
ただひたすらに 夜を待つよ
Just earnestly waiting for the night.
このままじゃ どんどんダメになりそう
Like this, it seems I'll gradually become useless.
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
Wait for the night, wait for the night.
きっと散々な目にあいそう
Surely, I'll face a miserable time.
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
Wait for the night, waiting for it.
耐え抜いて ざんざん雨に降られて
Enduring, getting soaked in the drizzling rain,
夜を待つよ 君を待つよ 待つのよ
Wait for the night, wait for you, waiting for it.
今は待つのよ
Now, I'm waiting for it.
唇で ゆっくりゆっくり騙して
With my lips, slowly, slowly deceiving,
ぼくはポップで チープなふりして
I'll pretend to be pop and cheap,
真夜中までの夕暮れを泳いでは
Swimming through the dusk until midnight.
もののけはうっとり うそつき笑って
The mononoke are enraptured, lying and laughing,
導火線が燃える中で 今
Now, while the fuse is burning,
嘘をつくの 夜が来るまでは
I'll tell a lie until the night comes.
夜が明ける 千年前からぼくら
A thousand years before the night breaks, we...
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
Wait for the night, wait for the night.
君がぜんぜん わからないから
Because I don't understand you at all,
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
Wait for the night, waiting for it.
無理筋なペンチャン待ちでもいいの
Even an impossible Pen-chan wait is fine.
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ 待つのよ
Wait for the night, wait for the night, waiting for it.
君を待つのよ
I'm waiting for you.
そうよもっと 切先を研ぐのよ
Yes, more, sharpen the tip of the blade,
最後最後 絶対笑うのよ
Finally, finally, I'll definitely laugh!
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
Wait for the night, waiting for it.
最後最後 笑うのはぼくらだ
Finally, finally, the ones who will laugh are us.
だって僕は星だから stellar stellar
'Cause I am a star, stellar stellar.
きっと君もう気づいていた
I'm sure you had already noticed.
僕の心の奥で描いた
Drawn deep within my heart,
それがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
That's the cliched monologue I'll tell from now on.
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say,
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
A wall that could never be broken down, all this time.
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが
The scent of morning wafting in the air suddenly,
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
Was somehow unbearably hateful.
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていていた
I'd hug my knees in the corner of my room and tremble.
太陽なんかいらないから
I don't need the sunshine,
明けなまいでいて
Can dawn please stay away?
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Reach out your hand so it reaches someone.
僕だって君と同じ 特別なんかじゃないから
I'm just like you, nothing special at all.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I'll sing through the night, stellar stellar,
ありったけの輝きで
Shining with all the brilliance I have.
今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
Tonight, the music will never, ever stop.
そうだよ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
What I always wanted to be isn't...
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
A Cinderella waiting around,
迎えに行く王子様だ
But the prince going to greet her.
だって僕は星だから
'Cause I am a star.
なんて ありふれた話なんだ
What a common story this is.
理想だけ書き連ねていた
I was just writing down my ideals.
きっとあの星も泣いてるんだ
I'm sure that star is crying, too.
ノートの隅に眠るほんのワンシーンだ
Just a single scene sleeping in my notebook.
明日なんて来ないままでいて
Can tomorrow please just stay away?
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Reach out your hand so it reaches someone.
本当に大切なものは
Truly important things...
目に見えないようなんだ
Seem to be invisible to the eye.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
So I'll sing through the night, stellar stellar,
ありのまま考えないでで
Without overthinking, just as I am,
今宵音楽はきっときっと止まらない
Tonight, my music will surely, surely never stop.
そうだよ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
What I always wanted to be isn't...
あかぬけないヒロインじゃないさ
A fragile heroine,
救いに行くヒーローだ
But the hero going to save her.
夢見がちなとなおとぎ話
A dreamy fairy tale.
だって僕は星だから
Just like the shooting star I have become
Stellar Stellar
きっと思えばもう気付いていた
I'm sure that you've already seen through it all
僕の心の奥で描いたそれがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
This script hidden deep down in my heart that I will now read out, acting the part
A cliched monologue
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There are so many things I couldn't say out loud
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
So many walls I could never climb beyond, it never ends
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが どうしようもなく憎々しくて
Sensing the scent of morning wafting in the air,
I tried to fight it filling me with hate
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていた
I sat in a corner and cried into my knees, trembling all the while
太陽なんていらないから 明けないでいて
I don't need the sunshine, don't want it in my life
Can dawn please stay away?
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Hold your hand out all the way and reach out to make someone feel
僕だって君と同じ 特別なんじゃじやないから
We're very alike, indeed, both you and me, neither of us is special
そうさ僕は夜を歌う Stellar Stellar
So I sing now through this night, Stellar Stellar
ありったけの輝いて 今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
Shining as bright as any eye can take, my music will never ever be stopped tonight
そうさ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
So I say, what I wanted to be was never
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
A Cinderella who waits forever
迎えに行く王子様だ
But the prince who goes and gets things done
だって僕は星だから
Just like the shooting star I have become
だって僕は星だから Stellar Stellar
Stellar Stellar
きっと思えばもう気付いていた
I'm sure that you've already seen through it all
僕の心の奥で描いたそれがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
This script hidden deep down in my heart that I will now read out, acting the part
A cliched monologue
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There are so many things I couldn't say out loud
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
So many walls I could never climb beyond, it never ends
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが どうしようもなく憎々しくて
Sensing the scent of morning wafting in the air,
I tried to fight it filling me with hate
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていた
I sat in a corner and cried into my knees, trembling all the while
太陽なんていらないから 明けないでいて
I don't need the sunshine, don't want it in my life
Can dawn please stay away?
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Hold your hand out all the way and reach out to make someone feel
僕だって君と同じ 特別なんかじゃないから
We're very alike, indeed, both you and me, neither of us is special
そうさ僕は夜を歌う Stellar Stellar
So I sing now through this night, Stellar Stellar
ありったけの輝いて 今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
Shining as bright as any eye can take, my music will never ever be stopped tonight
そうさ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
So I say, what I wanted to be was never
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
A Cinderella who waits forever
迎えに行く王子様だ
But the prince who goes and gets things done
だって僕は星だから Stellar Stellar
Just like the shooting star I have become
Stellar Stellar
あの黄昏も折り畳めば静寂
That twilight, too, if folded up, would be silence
僕らの街じゃ暗がりは合図だ
In our town, the darkness is a signal
灯を消してはじめよう幕よ開け
Let's turn off the lights and begin, let the curtain rise
見上げ願いをあなたのように
Look up and make a wish, just like you
変わらず在っていたい
I want to remain unchanged
きらめきのヴェールを
A veil of sparkle
目元に箒星描いて
Drawing a shooting star on my eyelids
瞬いたソワレ 今だ!
Twinkling Soiree, it's now!
あの黄昏も折り畳めば静寂
If you fold up that twilight, it becomes silence.
僕らの街じゃ暗がりは合図だ
In our town, the darkness is the signal.
灯を消してはじめよう 幕を開け
Turn off the lights and begin; let the curtain rise.
見上げ願いをあなたのように
Looking up, I make a wish, just like you.
変わらず在っていたい きらめきのヴェールを
I want to stay unchanged, wearing a veil of glitter.
瞬いたソワレ今だ！
It’s a twinkling soirée, now’s the time!
寝息を立てる太陽の目を盗んで
Stealing a glance at the sleeping sun,
大脱走さ逃げ出そうぜ
It’s a great escape, let’s run away.
朝未き空を跨ぐ栞を挟んだら
If we tuck in a bookmark that crosses the pre-dawn sky,
行かなくちゃソワレ
We have to go, soirée.
夜が明けるまでさ もう少しこのままで
Until the night breaks, just a little longer, like this.
あの鐘の音は茜差したって止まない
That bell's sound doesn't stop even when the madder red shines.
時間だ集まろう野望に喝采エールを
It’s time, let’s gather; send applause and cheers to our ambition.
未来の話を寂しそうに聞いてる君に
To you, who listens to stories of the future so lonely,
誓うよ世界に魔法がなくなってたって
I swear, even if there’s no magic in the world,
夢は続いていく
The dream will continue.
おやすみに代わるように
As if replacing 'good night',
鳴りやまないメロディー届けて
Deliver a melody that never stops ringing.
見逃すなソワレ僕ら目撃者だ
Don't miss it, soirée; we are the witnesses.
蒼穹に手を伸ばした
We reached our hands out to the blue sky.
水平線がうたた寝したって
Even if the horizon takes a nap,
とどめなく日々をつなぐ架け橋渡ったら
If we cross the bridge that endlessly connects our days,
いつの日かソワレ君に届くまでさ
Someday, soirée, until it reaches you,
何度でも呼び声を
I’ll call out to you again and again.
star tail 消せない軌跡辿って
Star tail, following the trajectory that won't disappear,
star tale 幾星霜の果てへどこまでも
Star tale, to the ends of ages, wherever it goes.
一晩じゃ語り尽くせない悲劇も
Even tragedies that can’t be fully told in one night,
一晩中語り明かしたら喜劇になっていく
If we talk through the whole night, they become comedies.
star tail 聞かせてよ star tail 一筋の star tale
Star tail, let me hear it. Star tail, a single star tale.
瞬いたソワレ今だ！
It’s a twinkling soirée, now’s the time!
寝息を立てる太陽の目を盗んで
Stealing a glance at the sleeping sun,
大脱走さ逃げ出そうぜ
It’s a great escape, let’s run away.
朝未き空を跨ぐ栞を挟んだら
If we tuck in a bookmark that crosses the pre-dawn sky,
約束だソワレ僕が眠るまでは
It's a promise, soirée; until I fall asleep,
何度でもまた明日
Again and again, see you tomorrow.
一晩じゃ語り尽くせない悲劇も
Even tragedies that can’t be fully told in one night,
一晩中語り明かしたら喜劇になっていく
If we talk through the whole night, they become comedies.
聞かせてよ star tail
Let me hear it, star tail,
一筋の star tale
a single star tale.
瞬いたソワレ今だ！
It’s a twinkling soirée, now’s the time!
寝息を立てる太陽の目を盗んで
Stealing a glance at the sleeping sun,
大脱走さ逃げ出そうぜ
It’s a great escape, let’s run away.
朝未き空を跨ぐ栞を挟んだら
If we tuck in a bookmark that crosses the pre-dawn sky,
約束だソワレ僕が眠るまでは
It's a promise, soirée; until I fall asleep,
何度でもまた明日
Again and again, see you tomorrow.
拝啓、ソワレ君へ紡ぎ継がれる
Dear soirée, passed down to you,
私たちの物語
the story of us.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
以上、星街すいせいでした！
That's all, this was Hoshimachi Suisei!
お疲れ様です！配信見てくれてますか？
Good work! Are you watching the stream?
もちろん です。本当に、お疲れ様です。
Of course. Truly, great work.
この後、あの件発表してきます。
After this, I'm going to announce that matter.
胸を張って、自信を持ってお話ししてきてください。
Please speak with pride and confidence.
はい！頑張ります！
Yes! I'll do my best!
改めて、配信記念生配信を見てくれて本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for watching the live stream celebrating our 5th anniversary today.
今日は、私星街すいせいから、皆さんに重大な発表があります。
Today, I, Hoshimachi Suisei, have a major announcement for you all.
これまで長年、カバーさん、そしてホロライブプロダクションには本当にお世話になってきました。
I've been truly indebted to Cover Corp and Hololive Production for many years.
長年の夢だった日本武道館などたくさんの支えのおかげで、夢を一つ一つ叶えていくことができました。
With the incredible support of the Nippon Budokan and so many others, I've been able to achieve my dreams one by one.
感謝の気持ちを伝えられる機会がこれまであまりなかったのですが、たにかおさんをはじめ、ホロライブのタレントのみんな、スタッフの皆さん、関係してくださった皆さんに心から感謝をしています。ありがとうございます。
I don't often get the chance to express my gratitude, but from the bottom of my heart, thank you so much to everyone—Taniago-san, all the Hololive talent, and the staff who made this possible.
その上で、東京ドームという次の目標に到達するためには、これからどうすればいいのかを考えてきました。
To reach my next goal of the Tokyo Dome, I've been thinking about what I need to do moving forward.
昔に比べると、たくさんの方に見ていただけるようになりましたが、それでもまだまだ越えなければいけない壁がたくさんあります。
Compared to the past, I'm able to reach so many more people, but I still have many walls to climb.
いろんなものと真剣に向き合い、そして考え抜いた結果、一つの大きな決断を下しました。
After facing many things earnestly and thinking deeply, I've made a major decision.
びっくりさせてしまうかもしれませんが、その発表を今日、この場でさせてください。
I will be making that announcement right here, right now.
ということで、この度、星街すいせいは個人事務所を設立することになりました！
And so, this time, Hoshimachi Suisei is establishing a personal office!
名称は「STUDIO STELLAR」。
Its name is "STUDIO STELLAR."
今後の私個人の活動、日々の配信、音楽活動、メディア出演、タイアップ、グッズ展開などなど、すべてこの「STUDIO STELLAR」を拠点に行っていくことになります。
My future activities, daily streams, musical endeavors, media appearances, tie-ups, merchandise rollouts, and more will all be based out of this STUDIO STELLAR.
と、こんな真面目なトーンで話すと「えっ、すいちゃん、ホロライブ卒業！？」なんてね、おもっちゃう人もいるんじゃないでしょうか？安心してください！
If you're talking in such a serious tone and thinking, "Suichan, did you graduate from Hololive?!" please rest assured!
ホロライブプロダクションとしての星街すいせいの活動も、これまで通り継続していきます。
Hoshimachi Suisei's activities as a Hololive Production talent will continue just as before.
ホロライブの大好きなみんなとの活動は引き続き思い切り楽しみつつ、個人としてのさらなる高みを目指す場所が「STUDIO STELLAR」という住み分けです。
I will continue to wholeheartedly enjoy my activities with my beloved Hololive port, while STUDIO STELLAR will be the place where I aim for even greater heights as an individual.
もっともっと大きなステージに立つための前向きで大きな決断なので、ぜひこれからも応援してもらえるとすごく、すごく嬉しいです！
It's a forward-looking, major decision to stand on an even bigger stage, so I'd be so, so happy if you continue to support me from now on!
ちなみに、事務所の公式SNSもできましたので、今すぐフォローしてください！IDは@st_stellar_infoです。
By the way, the office's official social media is now up, so please follow it right away! The ID is @st_stellar_info.
この個人事務所設立をキッカケに、星街すいせいを構成するあらゆるクリエイティブをリニューアルしていきます。どんどん発表していきますよ！準備はいいですか？
Triggered by the establishment of this personal office, I will be renewing everything that makes up Hoshimachi Suisei creatively. I'll be announcing more soon, so is everyone ready?
それでは、1つ目、長年愛してきた星街すいせいのロゴをリニューアルさせていただきました！こちら！
First, the logo for Hoshimachi Suisei, whom you've loved for so many years, has been renewed. Here it is!
これまでの歴史とトーンはしっかり踏襲しつつ、今の時代に、そして今の私に一番フィットする形にデザインし直しました。さらに、ずっと欲しかった私のシンボルマークもなんと新しく誕生しましたよ！こちら。いかがですか？可愛いね、王冠マークになっております。
It's been redesigned to carry on my history and tone while fitting the current era and who I am today. And my symbol mark, which I've always wanted, has finally been born too! Here it is. Isn't it a cute crown mark?
お次はアーティスト写真です。どうぞ！
Next is the artist photo. Go ahead!
はい、今回は夜の海で撮影してもらいました。これからの果てしない旅を感じさせるお気に入りの1枚になっております。
Yes, this time it was shot at night by the sea. It has become one of my favorite photos, giving a sense of endless travel.
まだまだありますよ！実は、これまでずっとなかったすいちゃんの公式ウェブサイトがとうとうオープンします！最新情報だったり随時アップデートしていくので、毎日チェックしてくださいね。
There's still more! Actually, Suichan's official website has finally opened! It will be updated with the latest information, so be sure to check it daily, okay?
そしてそして、皆さんきっと待ち望んであろう、公式ファンクラブも設立が決定しました！名前は「星詠み」。
And finally, everyone, the official fan club you've all been waiting for has been decided! Its name is "Hoshiyomi."
ファンクラブの名前さにさせていただきました。
I made it the name of the fan club.
これからももっとみんなの近くでいろんなことを発信していきたいと思います。
I want to keep communicating various things closer to everyone from now on.
ファンクラブ限定グッズが買えたりチケットの先行申し込みができたり、
Fan club exclusive goods can be bought, advance ticket applications can be made,
解放しラジオコンテンツなどなど、ファンクラブのためにいろいろ準備しているので入会をお待ちしております！
radio content, etc., preparing various things for the fan club, so we look forward to your enrollment!
入会はこの配信終了後21時からです。
Enrollment starts at 21:00 after this stream ends.
ファンクラブができたということは次に何が来るかお分かりですよね？
Since the fan club has been created, you know what comes next, right?
それではVTRどうぞ！
Now, here is the VTR!
なんと！星街すいせいアリーナツアーまたしても開催決定ありがとうございます！どどん！
What! Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour decided to be held again, thank you! Ta-da!
タイトルは「Once Upon a Stellar」。今回は4会場5公演でお届けします。
The title is "Once Upon a Stellar." We will deliver across 4 venues and 5 shows.
9月8日、9月9日のKアリーナ横浜2daysを皮切りに、
Starting with K Arena Yokohama 2-days on September 8th and 9th,
10月21日にGLION ARENA KOBE、11月7日にナゴヤIGアリーナ、
GLION ARENA KOBE on October 21st, Nagoya IG Arena on November 7th,
そして11月12日にマリンメッセ福岡A館、星街すいせい初となる4都市アリーナツアー、ぜひ遊びに来てください！
and Marine Messe Fukuoka Hall A on November 12th—Hoshimachi Suisei's first 4-city arena tour, please come!
お気づきの方もねいると思うんですけれども、今回のライブキービジュアルもMika Pikazoさんに…
I think some of you noticed, this live key visual was also by Mika Pikazo...
加藤っ…お気づきの方もいるかもしれませんが出した
Kato... some of you might have noticed, but...
今回のライブキービジュアルはMika Pikazo先生に描き下ろしていただきました！
The key visual for this live was drawn by Mika Pikazo-sensei!
美香先生本当にありがとうございます！今回も本当に素敵なキービジュアルでね、あのぜひたくさんね見てください。
Mika-sensei, thank you so much! It's such a wonderful key visual, so please go check it out a lot.
チケットはなんと本日の配信終了後から早速ファンクラブ先行申し込みがスタートします！絶対絶対チェックしてくださいね！
Tickets will start advance fan club applications right after today's stream ends! Be sure to check it out!
はい、次、実はもう一つ騒がれていたあの大きなプロジェクトが動き出します。それではVTRをどうぞ！
Yes, next, actually another big project that was whispered about is starting. Now, here is the VTR!
ハロー ハロー ハロー
Hello hello hello
幕はもう開いているんだずっと
The curtain is already open
今真空さえ揺らして響かせる
Even the vacuum now shakes and resonates
そんな音楽を！
Such music!
さあ
Here we go
切り裂く静寂
Silence of cutting
全速前進
Full speed forward
生み出す引力で
With the gravitational force
光速のパッセージ
Light speed passage
アレグロで今日も舞って
Dance today in allegro
わなわな響音
Roaring sound
show must go on
The show must go on
消えない一音を
A beat that does not disappear
もっと紡いで
Spinning more
打ち鳴らせ今日も万全で！
Play thoroughly today!
しばらく眠っていたあのプロジェクト、Midnight Grand Orchestraも活動を改めて本格化していきます！
That project that had been asleep, Midnight Grand Orchestra, will also fully resume its activities!
タイトルは「プロジェクト アレグロ」。日程は2027年2月11日、場所は幕張メッセにてライブを行います。
The title is "Project Allegro." The date is February 11, 2027, and the live will be held at Makuhari Messe.
こちらも本日からもファンクラブで先行申し込みができるのでぜひぜひ遊びに来てください！
Advance fan club applications start today for this as well, so please come join us!
リリースだったりタイアップなどすでにいろいろ決まっているものもありますので、星街すいせい、そしてMidnight Grand Orchestraのこれからを楽しみにしていいてくれると嬉しいです！
There are already various things decided like releases and tie-ups, so we hope you'll look forward to the future of Hoshimachi Suisei and Midnight Grand Orchestra!
さて、すごい勢いで情報を出していきましたが、みなさんついてこれておりますか？
Now, we've put out information at a breakneck speed—are you all able to keep up?
今日発表したことは全部ね、次の大きな目標に向けて私が本当に頑張りたいと思ってたくさん悩んだ末に決断をしたことです。
Everything announced today is a decision I made after agonizing over wanting to work hard toward my next big goal.
環境は少し変わるかもしれないんですが、星街すいせいはもちろんこれからもずっと私らしくあり続けます。
The environment might change slightly, but Hoshimachi Suisei will of course continue to be herself.
これからもどうか一緒に夢を追いかけてくれると嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします！
We'd be so happy if you continue chasing dreams with us. Thank you for your support!
さて、それでは最後に3つ…まだ3つもある。3つだけお知らせをして今日の配信を終わりたいと思います。
Well then, finally three... wait, still three more. With just three announcements, I'd like to end today's stream.
まず
First...
今日は皆さんお忘れじゃないですよね?
Today, everyone, I'm sure you haven't forgotten, right?
私の誕生日でもあるということで、生誕グッズをもちろんご用意しております!
Today is my birthday, so of course, I've got birthday goods prepared!
Tシャツ、ステッカーセット、アクリルスタンド、全部入りボックスに加えて、ファンクラブ限定のTシャツなどなど、どれもデザインにこだわりましたので、ぜひ手に入れてください!
T-shirts, sticker sets, acrylic stands, all included in the full set box, plus fan club-exclusive T-shirts and more. Every item has been designed with so much care, so please make sure to get your hands on them!
2つ目
Second...
星街すいせいLive Tour 2024 Spectrum of Nova、星街すいせい日本武道館ライブSuperNova、この2つのBlu-rayの通常盤が予約受付開始します!予約は本日22時からスタートです。
The regular Blu-ray editions of "Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 Spectrum of Nova" and "Hoshimachi Suisei Nippon Budokan Live SuperNova" are now open for pre-order! Pre-orders start today at 22:00.
今回のBlu-rayは以前のようなセット販売はなく、ツアー・武道館それぞれ個別での販売のみになります。そしてツアーのBlu-rayは埼玉公演のみの映像化となっています。
This time, unlike previous releases, there won't be set sales; the tour and Budokan Blu-rays will be sold separately, and the tour Blu-ray will feature footage exclusively from the Saitama concert.
ただし、特典映像として他のツアー公演の楽曲も一部収録されております!ゲストパートとか。何が収録されているかはぜひBlu-rayでチェックしてみてください!
However, it will also include select songs from other tour concerts as special footage—like guest parts! Be sure to check the Blu-ray to see what's included!
なお、今回は去年販売したBlu-rayとは仕様が少し異なり、ツアーBlu-rayの特典映像以外の特典は付属していませんのでご注意ください。ただ、その分ね、お求めやすい価格になっておりますので、詳しくは特設サイトや公式X、公式Twitterをチェックしてください!
Note that unlike last year's Blu-ray, there are no additional bonuses aside from the special tour footage, but because of that, they're available at a more affordable price. For details, please check the special website, our official X, or official Twitter!
そして3つ目!
And third...
皆さん、お待たせしました!毎年恒例ですが、新曲が出ます!
Everyone, thank you for waiting! Every year, as is tradition... a new song is coming out!
タイトルは「プリマドンナ」!
The title is "Prima Donna"!
この配信が終わった後、21:30からミュージックビデオのプレミア公開が始まります!これからの星街すいせいの名刺代わりになるような、すごくテンションが上がる曲に仕上がっております。概要欄に貼っているURLから飛べるので、ぜひ楽しみにしていてください!絶対に待機していてください。
The music video premiere starts tonight at 21:30, right after this stream ends! It's a song that really gets your adrenaline pumping, almost like it could be Hoshimachi Suisei's new signature name-drop track. You can jump to it via the URL in the description, so please look forward to it! Make sure you're ready and waiting!
ということで、以上で星街すいせい6周年記念生誕配信を終わります。
With that, this concludes the Hoshimachi Suisei 6th Anniversary Birthday Stream.
今日は本当にありがとうございました!
Thank you all so very much today!
新しいスタジオステラの星街すいせも、どうかどうかよろしくお願いいたします!
And I hope you'll continue to support the new Studio Stellar version of Hoshimachi Suisei!
それでは、またねー!
Well then... bye-bye!
照らす一筋のlight
A single ray of light shining down,
注ぐ無数の視線like stars
Countless pouring gazes like stars.
独り占めしたいその心
I want to monopolize that heart.
幕が上がればact 1
If the curtains open up, act 1.
Yeah, are you ready now?
Suisei, here I come
そこ空けて
Open that there,
譲れないわmy stage
not giving up my stage.
邪魔しないでよね
Don't get in my way,
Make upしてdress up
I put on makeup and dress up.
待ってるひとがいるのyeah
As people are waiting for me, yeah.
ところでそちらどちら様ですか?
Are we good already?
もういいですか?主役って大変だわ
Being the lead is rough.
Pop pop ノイズを消して
Pop pop, turn off the noise,
目と目逸らさないでね
and eye to eye, don't turn away, ok?
プリマドンナ
Prima donna,
冷笑にはもうウンザリだわ
the snark is already boring.
熱いheart music
A passionate heart music
浴びたらspot light
if showered in the spotlight.
例えどんな嫌味も ごめん遊ばせ
No matter what sarcasm, please excuse me.
Wanna wanna go Gonna gonna go
No more time for goodbyes
賞賛絶賛ありがと
Thank you for the admiration and high praise,
All because of you, let's go
Chop chop
嫉妬妬み妬みからやってかみ
jealousy and envy are getting out of hand!
暇なんですか? jealousy?
Is it because you're that free? Jealousy?
I want it
誰にもそうanymoreこのstoryを
Everyone is the same, is there anymore to this story?
I want it
ご機嫌ようね
Greetings and adieu,
Whoa oh yeah
Pop pop フラッシュを浴びて
Pop pop, the flash rains down on me,
耳を離さないでね
don't separate your ears from me, ok?
感じる? 扉が開くように
Do you feel it? Like the door is open,
飛び込む世界は回る
the world we jumped into goes around.
君と見たいall i need is you
I want to see it with you, all I need is you.
続く未来にきっと夢中
I'm surely absorbed in this continuing future,
Light on me 輝け
Light on me, shine!
最後までみてくれてありがとう☆彡
Thank you for watching until the end!
これからも私は私らしく、みんなと共にあります。
I will stay true to myself and walk with everyone.
新しい挑戦を続けて、まだ見ぬ世界を見に行こう！
Continuing new challenges,
let's see an unseen world!